Guide to the Jonathan Warner Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Jonathan Warner papers
1836-1887
WA MSS S-2925
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1.34
(5 boxes)
Papers of Jonathan Warner and his family of Jefferson in Ashtabula County, Ohio, 1836-1887. Correspondence documents the activities of Warner's immediate and extended family, and documents their opinions on sectionalism and slavery. The collection includes letters written by his brother, George Washington Warner, which document his emigration to California in 1852, as well as his activities in Washington Territory and Idaho Territory until 1865. Business records in the collection chiefly consist of deeds, contracts, and other legal instruments related to real estate transactions in Ashtabula County, as well as property tax assessments.
Warner, Jonathan, 1812-1888
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from William Reese Company (Cowan's Auctions' sale, 2009 December 9, lot 349) on the William Robertson Coe Fund No. 3, 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Jonathan Warner, IV (1812-1888)
Jonathan Warner, IV, also known as Jonathan Warner, Jr., was a farmer and landowner in Jefferson, Ohio. He was the son of Nancy Frethy Warner (1789-1881) and Jonathan Warner, III (1782-1862), who was the recorder of deeds (1815-1822) and treasurer (1825) for Ashtabula County, as well as a member of the the Ohio House of Representatives in 1831 and an Associate Judge of the Court of Common Pleas from 1839 to 1846. Warner had ten siblings, including a brother with the same name who died in infancy: Nancy Warner Holman (1808-1885), Phebe Warner King (1815-1893), Adeline Lovina Warner Ranney (1818-1900), Jane Warner Starr (1820-1892), Louisa Warner Simonds (1823-1899), George Washington Warner (1825-1877), Isabelle "Bell" Warner Moore Ducro (1828-1913), Francis H. Warner (1831-1904), and Charles Ely Warner (1834-1906).
In 1839, Warner married Lydia Allen Warner (1815-1843). After the death of his first wife, he married Catherine Krum Warner (1821-1885) in 1848, and they had three children: Flora Isabel Warner Ives (1850-1942), Lena Evelyn Warner Pritchard (1858-1938), and Howard Jonathan Warner (1860-1940).
George Washington Warner (1825-1877)
George Washington Warner was a brother of Jonathan Warner, Jr. He worked in gold mines near the Klamath River in northern California and around Walla Walla, Washington. He eventually operated a farm and raised livestock in Wallula, Washington. In 1872, he married Matilda Ann Burdett Warner (1849-1930), and they had two children, Jessie Louise Warner Kuhlenecamp (1873-1954) and George Washington Warner, Jr. (1875-1963). He died from a gunshot wound while hunting.
Scope and Contents
Papers of Jonathan Warner and his family from Jefferson, Ashtabula County, Ohio, 1836-1887. Correspondence documents the activities of Warner's immediate and extended family, including their opinions on sectionalism and slavery. The collection includes letters written by his brother, George Washington Warner, which document his emigration to California in 1852, as well as his activities in Washington Territory and Idaho Territory until 1865. Business records in the collection chiefly consist of deeds, contracts, and other legal instruments related to real estate transactions in Ashtabula County, as well as property tax assessments.
The collection includes a letter from Jonathan Warner's cousin Matthew Griswold Warner in January 1852, which discusses the activities of another cousin, Jonathan Trumbull Warner, also known as Juan Jose Warner, in Agua Caliente, California. The letter details conflict with American Indians led by a Cupeño Indian, Antonio Garra, during the Yuma War, 1850-1853.
Letters by George Washington Warner describe his voyage to California via Panama in March-April 1852, as well as a subsequent visit with Juan José Warner. His later correspondence discusses gold mining in California at Gold Hill in Nevada County, as well as near Trinidad and near the Klamath River in Humboldt County. Realia in the collection includes a small gold nugget, presumably mined by Warner. In letters from 1863 to 1865, Warner discusses his work driving mule teams between Walla Walla, Washington Territory, and Boise, Idaho Territory.
A group of correspondence with extended family and others, 1884-1886, relate to efforts by the Warner family to receive spoliation claim money from the French related to their capture of the brig Matilda during the Quasi-War between the United States and France.
Arrangement
Organized into three series: I. Correspondence, 1836-1887. II. Business and Property Records, 1840-1887. III. Realia, circa 1860-circa 1870.
Cupeño Indians; Indians of North America -- California; Indians of North America -- Wars -- 1815-1875; Sectionalism (United States) -- Public opinion; Slavery -- United States -- Public opinion; Voyages to the Pacific coast; Agua Caliente (Calif.) -- Description and travel; Ashtabula County (Ohio) -- Description and travel; Boise (Idaho) -- Description and travel; California -- Description and travel; California -- Gold discoveries; France -- Foreign relations -- United States; Gold Hill (Nevada County, Calif.) -- Description and travel; Humboldt County (Calif.) -- Description and travel; Idaho Territory -- Description and travel; Jefferson (Ashtabula County, Ohio) -- Description and travel; Klamath River (Or. and Calif.) -- Description and travel; Ohio -- Description and travel; Panama -- Description and travel; Trinidad (Calif.) -- Description and travel; United States -- Foreign relations -- France; United States -- Politics and government -- 1797-1801; Walla Walla (Wash.) -- Description and travel; Washington (State) -- Description and travel; Gold (metal); Garra, Antonio, -1852; Warner family; Warner, George Washington, 1825-1877; Warner, J. J. (Juan José), 1807-1895; Warner, Jonathan, 1812-1888; Warner, Matthew Griswold, 1799-1884
- Correspondence, 1836-1887; Series I; 0.42; (1 box)
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically followed by correspondence with no identified years and orphaned envelopes.
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, chiefly by family members and business associates of Jonathan Warner, Jr.
  Many letters are accompanied by their original envelopes.
  - Marsh, J. S., et al., Jefferson, Ohio, invitation to an Independence Ball to Jonathan Warner, Jr., and Dolly Anne Handsom, Jefferson, Ohio, 1836 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Benjamin, Kinsman, Ohio, letter to Lydia Allen Warner and Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1843 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Pratt, Ann, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1844 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Starr, George, Hudson, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, as well as a letter from Jane Starr, Hudson, Ohio, to Phebe Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1845 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Warner, Jonathan ("Cousin"), Chester, Connecticut, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1847 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Biographical/Historical note
    Jonathan Warner (1823-1905) and Sarah Warner Silliman (born 1820) were children of Ely Warner (1785-1872) and Sarah Ward Warner (1798-1886) in Chester, Connecticut.
    With a letter from Sarah Warner Silliman to Phebe Warner.
  - Warner, Jared Clark, Chester, Connecticut, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1848 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Jared Clark Warner (1829-1855, Yale 1854) was the son of Ely Warner (1785-1872) and Sara Ward Warner (1798-1886).
  - Krum, Abel, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1848 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Abel Krum (1805-1881) was a brother of Catherine Krum Warner.
  - Lobdell, Fanny Krum, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner and Elvira Lobdell, Jefferson, Ohio, 1849 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Fanny Krum Lobdell (1808-1882) was a sister of Catherine Krum Warner.
    Elvira Lobdell (born 1834) was a daughter of Fanny Krum Lobdell and Lockwood Lobdell (born 1805).
  - Warner, Jared Clark, Detroit, Michigan, letters to Jonathan Warner, George Washington Warner, and Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1849?, March 27 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Krum, Abel, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1849 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Flora A. Krum Regal (1832-1899) was a daughter of Abel Krum and Mary Brower Krum (born 1807).
    With a letter from Flora A. Krum to Catherine Krum Warner.
  - Krum, Abel, Columbus, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., and Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1850 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Root, Ezekiel C., Ashtabula, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1850 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lobdell, Elvira, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1850 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Warner, Jonathan ("Cousin"), Chester, Connecticut, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1850 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Warner, Jonathan ("Cousin"), Chester, Connecticut, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1851 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Warner, Matthew Griswold, Rochester, New York, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Matthew Griswold Warner (1799-1884) was the son of Selden Warner (1760-1843) and Dorothy Selden Warner (1766-1825) and the city treasurer of Rochester, New York in 1847.
  - Krum, Sarah Trowbridge, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Sarah Trowbridge Krum (born 1781) was the mother of Catherine Krum Warner.
  - Warner, George Washington, Havana, Cuba, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Warner, George Washington, aboard ship to California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Warner, George Washington, aboard ship to California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Moore (later Ducro), Isabelle "Bell" Warner, West Greenville, Mercer, Pennsylvania, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Warner, George Washington, Gold Hill, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Warner, George Washington, Trinidad, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Miles, H. B., Madison, Wisconsin, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Warner, George Washington, Gold Hill, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Warner, George Washington, Gold Hill, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1852 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Krum, Abel, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1853 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Warner, George Washington, Gold Hill, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1853 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Warner, George Washington, Salmon River, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1854 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Warner, Francis H., Shakopee, Minnesota, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., and Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, 1855 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Warner, George Washington, Trinidad, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1856 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Warner, George Washington, Klamath River, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1857 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Warner, George Washington, Klamath River, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1858 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Warner, George Washington, Klamath River, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1858 July 24? (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Warner, George Washington, Klamath River, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1861 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Warner, Jonathan, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, letter to the postmaster of Orleans Bar, Klamath County, California, 1863 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Letter inquires about George Washington Warner, who had not communicated with him for over eighteen months.
  - Jenks, Bela Whipple, postmaster, Orleans, California, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1863 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Letter reports that George Washington Warner, reportedly traveled to mines near Walla Walla, Washington Territory.
  - Warner, Jonathan, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, letter to the postmaster of Orleans Bar, Klamath County, California, 1864 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Letter states that correspondence to George Washington Warner in Walla Walla, Washington Territory, have returned to him, and requests the help of the postmaster to locate him.
    Includes an envelope addressed to George Washington Warner and with postmark date March 11, 1863, as well as a return letter envelope with postmark date October 27, 1864.
  - Jenks, Bela Whipple, postmaster, Orleans, California, letter to George Washington Warner, Walla Walla, Washington Territory, 1864 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Includes envelopes addressed to George Washington Warner in Idaho City, Idaho, and to Jonathan Warner, Jr., in Jefferson, Ohio.
  - Warner, George Washington, Walla Walla, Washington, letter to Warner, Jonathan, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1865 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Warner, Charles Ely, Chaska, Minnesota, letter to Warner, Jonathan, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1866 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Hayward, Samuel, Conneaut Mutual Loan Association, Conneaut, Ohio, account statement to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1874 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Hayward, Samuel, Conneaut Mutual Loan Association, Conneaut, Ohio, account statement to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1874 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Hayward, Samuel, Conneaut Mutual Loan Association, Conneaut, Ohio, letter of receipt to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1875 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - H. Peck & Son, Streetsboro, Ohio, postcard to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1880 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - H. Peck & Son, Streetsboro, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1880 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Foote, Morris Julius, First Auditor's Office, United States. Department of the Treasury, Washington, D.C., letter to Adeline Lovina Warner Ranney, Cleveland, Ohio, 1884 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Foote, Morris Julius, First Auditor's Office, United States. Department of the Treasury, Washington, D.C., letter to Adeline Lovina Warner Ranney, Cleveland, Ohio, 1884 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Foote, Morris Julius, First Auditor's Office, United States. Department of the Treasury, Washington, D.C., letter to Adeline Lovina Warner Ranney, Cleveland, Ohio, 1884 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Foote, Morris Julius, Washington, D.C., letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1885 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Sindsley, D. C., Cleveland, Ohio, letter to John Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1885 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Foote, Morris Julius, Washington, D.C., letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1885 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Warner, Andrew Ely, Chester, Connecticut, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1885 October 18? (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Enclosures include a letter from John B. Shipman, Coldwater, Michigan, to Andrew Ely Warner, October 17, 1885?, regarding receive spoliation claim money from the French for the capture of the brig Matilda.
    Andrew Ely Warner (1838-1920) was a son of Ely Warner and Sarah Ward Warner.
    John B. Shipman (1839-1918?) was a politician and attorney, as well as a judge for the 15th Circuit Court, Michigan, from 1879 to 1881.
  - Shipman, John B., Washington, D.C., letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1886 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Starr, Orlando Comfort, Rock Circle, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, 1887 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Orlando Comfort Starr was the son of Jane Warner Starr (1820-1892) and George Starr (1816-1875).
  - Smith, James P., Clark's Corner, Ohio, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, no year, January 12 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Bisma?, B. T., Philadelphia, letter to Jonathan Warner, Jr., Jefferson, Ohio, no year, January 18 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Krum, Sarah Trowbridge, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, no year, May 11 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Krum, Sarah Trowbridge, Cherry Valley, Ohio, letter to Catherine Krum Warner, Jefferson, Ohio, no year November 20 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Inside of recycled envelope originally addressed to Abel Krum, Esquire, Cherry Valley, Ohio, March 29
  - Orphan envelopes, various dates (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Business and Property Records, 1840-1887; Series II; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  Series II is organized into two subseries: Business Records and Property Tax Assessments
  Business records that chiefly consist of deeds, contracts, and other legal instruments related to real estate transactions in Ashtabula County, as well as property tax assessments.
  - Business Records
    Arranged chronologically
    - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1840 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1840 February 22
      Related Archival Materials note
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 134
    - Notes related to a warranty deed from Erastus Hulett to Abel Smith, probably in Conneaut, Ohio, 1842 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1846 January 31
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 135
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Joseph Addison Giddings to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1847 May 28
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 136
    - Contract for sale of land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Joseph Addison Giddings to Jonathan Warner and Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1847 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Contract for sale of land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Eben Newton and Elisha Whittelsey to Alvin Dudley, as well as the transfer of the contract to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1847 December 15, 1848 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Receipt of payment of bids to P. R. Spencer by Jonathan Warner and Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1848 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1848 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Joseph Addison Giddings to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1849 December 3
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 137
    - Contract for sale of land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Eben Newton, Mary S. Newton, Elisha Whittelsey, and Polly Whittelsey to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1853 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Order to the County Surveyor of Ashtabula County from the Auditor of Ashtabula County to survey a portion of land in Plymouth, Ohio, by John Olin to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1856 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Transfer deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1857 October 14 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Alvin Wood and Lydia Wood to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1863 November 9
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 138
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Alvin Wood and Lydia Wood to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1864 April 16
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 139
    - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner, Jr., to Alvin Wood, 1864 April 19
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 140
    - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner Jr., to Alvin Wood, 1864 September 5
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 141
    - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Stephen Hoskins to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1865 February 16
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 142
    - Record of accounts between Stephen Hoskins and Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1865 May 11- 1868 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Land contract for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from John A. Granger to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1866 November
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 143
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Elisha C. Pratt and Lovina C. Pratt to Jonathan Warner, 1871 September 20
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 144
    - Promissary note from Jonathan Warner, Jr., to J. C. Pratt, 1871 October 7 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Land contract for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner, Jr., to Dennis Williams, 1871 December 9
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 145
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, sold by John A. Granger to Jonathan Warner on November 30, 1866, 1872 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - J. Taylor, minutes of land surveyed in Jefferson, Ohio, for Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1873 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Contract for sale of land in Dorset, Ohio, from W. P. Howland and Michael Fitzgerald, as well as the transfer of the contract to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1875 May 17, 1878 January 1 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Mortgage deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Andrew Grimes and Emily Grimes to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1876 November 23
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 146
    - Agreement to sell of land in Morgan, Ashtabula County, Ohio, from Jonathan Warner, Jr., to G. W. Allen, 1877 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Record and receipt of payments, 1878 January 1 - 1880 January 1 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Mortgage of chattels for horses, wagons, and tack from Andrew Grimes to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1879 January 14
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 147
    - Warranty deed for land in Denmark and Jefferson, Ohio, from Andrew Grimes and Emily Grimes to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1880 February 18
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 148
    - Warranty deed for land in Jefferson, Ohio, from Willet J. Dickinson to Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1882 July 8
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 5, folder 149
    - Summons for Jonathan Warner, Jr., from the United States District Court (Ohio: Northern District) to testify in the case of the United States v. Stephen A. Northway, 1885 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Dorset Cheese Factory, receipt for milk purchased from Jonathan Warner, Jr., 1885 July 20 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Summons for Jonathan Warner, Jr., from the United States District Court (Ohio: Northern District) to testify in the case of the United States v. Stephen A. Northway, 1885 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Sketch map of a township, probably Jefferson, Ohio, which includes a courthouse and depot, as well as outlines of a farm, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Notes related to deeds and taxes, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Property Tax Assessments
    Arranged chronologically.
    Receipts for taxes assessed on property owned by Jonathan Warner, Jr., in Ashtabula County, Ohio.
    - Property tax assessments for the years 1840-1887, Jefferson, Ashtabula County, Ohio, 1840 December 9-1888 January 3 (Box 3, Folder 82-129)
- Realia, circa 1860-circa 1870; Series III; 0.21; (1 box)
  - Small gold nugget in a black metal lacquer oval box manufactured by Volupté cosmetics, circa 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Shoulder board for the uniform of a United States Army Colonel, circa 1860-1865 (Box 4, Folder 131)